// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "When did Sri Lanka become independent?",
    answer: "4 February 1948",
    options: [
      "30 June 1942",
      "4 February 1948",
      "4 July 1956",
      "2 December 1971"
    ],
    correct: false
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "If you go for a visit, you might find out that which of the following is a commonly used nickname for the beautiful island nation of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Pearl of the Indian Ocean",
    options: [
      "Muthuu",
      "Pearl of the Indian Ocean",
      "Rajapakshe",
      "All"
    ],
    correct: false
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which is the currency of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Rupee",
    options: [
      "Yen",
      "Rupee",
      "Baht",
      "Taka"
    ],
    correct: false
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How was Sri Lanka formerly known?",
    answer: "Ceylon",
    options: [
      "Nyasaland",
      "Ceylon",
      "Burmae",
      "Formosa"
    ],
    correct: false
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which is the longest river in Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Mahaweli",
    options: [
      "Cauvery",
      "Padma",
      "Mahaweli",
      "Amban"
    ],
    correct: false
  },

   {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which is the highest point in Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Pidurutalagala",
    options: [
      "Adamâ€™s Peak",
      "Godwin Austi",
      "Pidurutalagala",
      "Kirigalpott"
    ],
    correct: false
  },

    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "what is the most tourist attractive place in kandy?",
    answer: "Temple of the Sacred Tooth Relic",
    options: [
      "Sigiriya",
      "Yala National Park Safari",
      "Temple of the Sacred Tooth Relic",
      "Lesuire Wolrd"
    ],
    correct: false

  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the capital of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Sri Jayawardhanapura Kotte",
    options: [
      "Polonnaruwa",
      "Colombo",
      "Sri Jayawardhanapura Kotte",
      "Jaffna"
    ],
    correct: false

  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the traditional Sri Lankan greeting?",
    answer: "Ayubowan",
    options: [
      "Ayubowan",
      "Jumbo",
      "Bohoma Isthuthi",
      "Wanakkam"
    ],
    correct: false

  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In which Sri Lankan city, also the capital of the last independent kingdom in 1592, is the Esala Perahera festival held?",
    answer: "Kandy",
    options: [
      "Katunayake",
      "Kandana",
      "Kotte",
      "Kandy"
    ],
    correct: false

  },
  
];